REYHAN WIDYATNA HARWENDA

FRONTEND ENGINEER

Bekasi, Indonesia

+6281292316469

harwendareyhan@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Hi there, I'm a software engineer currently focused on frontend engineering with almost 2 years experience. I also like to dive deep into and cover all areas of software engineering. I'm also curious and willing to try new things like product management.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend Engineer

Twibbonize, Jakarta

Aug, 2021 - Oct, 2022

- Redevelop Twibbonize website with new design architecture, clean code design principle, better functionality and new user interface from scratch using NuxtJS and SCSS
- Refactoring all component into reusable component, implement state management concepts and develop our own styling CSS instead of using any CSS framework
- Add some extra features on campaign creation flow and reframe it with better functionality, interface and experience
- Handle image processing problems such as compressing image size, resizing image, change image format and pixel manipulation using canvas. Also work with third party canvas libraries to apply filter image and create text above image
- Developed a Button feature that allow users to add website link and published it to Twibbonize campaign
- Developed a Embed feature that allow users to embed their content on their social media platform to Twibbonize campaign, and currently there are six available social media that user can embed (YouTube, Twitter, Facebook, Tiktok, Spotify, Instagram)
- Developed a Media feature that allow users to post one or many photos/videos to Twibbonize campaign and download it as a participant
- Developed a Text feature that allow user to post their content/notes/guides or anything they want to show into Twibbonize campaign
- Developed a Comment feature that allows users to comment in campaign and interact with others by replying or mention other users in Twibbonize campaign
- Developed a Notification feature that allow users to get latest news from Twibbonize team
- Work closely and help product manager and UI/UX designer to design and develop new feature

INTERNSHIPS

Android Developer

Jun, 2019 - Aug, 2019

PT Aruna Jaya Nuswantara, Jakarta

- Develop real time chat application for Aruna internal team using Java and Firebase
- Build User Interfaces from Wire frames and Designs on Figma
- Collaborate with other developer using Git, GitHub, Trello

Software Engineer

Jul, 2020 - Aug, 2020

DSITD IPB, Bogor

Crawling website data using BeautifulSoup

- Develop dashboard management system that helps lecturers to check their grading index based on government grading index website using HTML, CSS, Python (Flask)
- Collaborate with other developer using Git, GitHub

EDUCATION

Computer Science

Bogor Agricultural University (IPB), Bogor

Sep, 2017 - Sep, 2021

PROJECTS

IPB Connect, Frontend Engineer

Jan, 2021 - Mar, 2021

- Redevelop IPB Connect website with clean code design principle, better functionality and new user interface from scratch using NuxtJS and Vuetify (CSS Framework)
- Implement state management concepts
- Build User Interfaces and Wire frames on Figma
- Work closely and Collaborate with Backend Engineer using GitHub

Project: https://ipbconnect.ipb.ac.id/

Twibbonize, Frontend Engineer

Aug, 2021 - Oct, 2022

- Redevelop Twibbonize website with new design architecture, clean code design principle, better functionality and new user interface from scratch using NuxtJS and SCSS
- Refactoring all component into reusable component, implement state management concepts and develop our own styling CSS instead of using any CSS framework
- Add some extra features on campaign creation flow and reframe it with better functionality, interface and experience
- Handle image processing problems such as compressing image size, resizing image, change image format and pixel manipulation using canvas.
- Work together and collaborate with other teams to develop many new features such as Button, Embed, Media, Text, Comment, Notification

Project: https://www.twibbonize.com/

SKILLS

Git

• C

PHP

HTML

• CSS/SCSS

Javascript

jQuery

React

Vue

Nuxt

COURSES

Des 2022	Dasar Pemrograman Javascript	Dicoding
Jan 2023	Fundamental FrontEnd Web	Dicoding Dicoding Dicoding
Jan 2023	Fundamental FrontEnd Web dengan React	
Feb 2023	React Web Developer Expert	
Feb 2023	FrontEnd Web Developer Expert	Dicoding

LANGUAGES